Hello.
こんにちは
It's cute.
可愛いですね
thank you.
ありがとうございます
That's a really stylish hairstyle.
すごいオシャレな髪型だね
thank you.
ありがとうございます
Are you wearing it yourself?
自分で着てるの?
I don't wear it myself.
自分で着てないです
I have meansis.
メアンシスついてます
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうなんだ
Eh, she looks like an idol.
えー、なんかアイドルみたい
Eh, is it true?
えー、本当ですか?
I haven't done it.
やってないです
やってない
You'll probably be called out to, right?
声かけられたりするでしょ?
No, I don't have one, but I admired it.
いや、ないけど、憧れてました
Did you admire it?
憧れてた?
I like idols.
アイドル好きなんだ
I kind of admired underground idols.
なんか、地下アイドルとか憧れてました
Oh, is that so?
あ、そうなの?
cute.
可愛い
cute?
可愛い?
cute.
可愛い
It's cute.
可愛いですよ
Thank you very much.
ありがとございます
Your hair is white.
白いね、髪が
Even Chima from Tohoku.
東北のチーマだって
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうなんだ
that's right.
そうです
Not born in Tohoku, isn't it?
東北の生まれじゃなくて、違う?
I'm originally from Hokkaido.
出身は北海道です
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうなんだ
that's right.
そうです
Wow, it turned out to be something white.
すごい、なんか白いものになったね
What do you usually do?
普段何してるんですか?
I usually work at a cafe.
普段カフェで働いてます
Oh, at a cafe?
あら、カフェで?
yes.
はい
It looks like a cafe, if you ask me.
カフェっぽいね、言われてみたら
Is it true?
本当ですか?
It's common.
よ くある
Are you making that?
あれ作ってるの?
Latte art.
ラテアート
I don't make latte art.
ラテアート、私作ってないです
Haven't you made it?
作ってない?
Ah, that's right.
ああ、そうなんだ
There is someone else who can make it.
他に作れる人がいると
Ah, I see.
ああ、なるほどね
Do you have a boyfriend now?
今、彼氏はいます?
I'm not there.
いないです
He's not there.
いないんだ
I think I have it.
持ってそう
I don't have it at all.
全然持ってないです
I think I have it.
持ってそう
It's true.
本当です
Haven't you had sex?
エッチしてない?
I haven't done it at all.
全然してない
That's a lie.
嘘だな
I was dumped, I said.
振られまして、言ったの
Will I get dumped?
振られるんだ?
Anyone you like can do it.
好きな人はできるんだ
Well, I guess I can't find someone I like,
え、なんか、好きな人はできないけど、
If you do it and start dating, you'll get dumped.
できて付き合ったら振られます
Will you get dumped after dating?
付き合ってから振られるの?
oh yeah.
そうそう
For what reason do you get rejected?
どういう理由で振られちゃう?
What did they say?
なんて言われたか
Anxiety or something.
不安とか
What do you mean?
どういうこと?
Anxiety.
不安って
I've been told that I'm jealous.
なんか、嫉妬するとか言われます
I guess I have a lot of other male friends.
ちょっと、他の男友の人が多いんだよね
Oh, that's a lot.
ああ、多いです
Ah, there are many.
あ、多いんだ
I wonder if my boyfriend will be jealous.
彼氏が嫉妬しちゃうのか、それで
Maybe so.
そうかも
I might actually get jealous.
確かに嫉妬しちゃうかもしれない
When was the last time you went edgy?
最近、いつエッジしたの?
Eh, when was that?
えー、いつだっけ?
Last month or so.
先月とか
Didn't you do that last week?
先週ってことしなかった?
Wasn't it last week?
先週じゃない?
No, no.
違う違う
Didn't you say it again?
言い直さなかった?
Really?
本当に?
I thought it was last month, but then I realized it was last month.
先月かなって思ったけど、 あ、先月だなって思った
Did you play Dalt?
ダルトしたの?
Dalt.
ダルト
Someone I'm curious about.
なんか、気になってる人
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
It makes me laugh so hard.
めっちゃ笑っちゃう
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Ah, yes.
あ、そう
I had an edge with a jealous person.
嫉妬する人とエッジしたの
Well, how was it?
えー、どうだった?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Are you going to stop here?
やめますか、この辺で
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいってね
You won't be able to stop laughing.
笑い止まらなくなっちゃうからね
But that's it, it's amazing.
でもあれだよね、すごい
Aren't your boobs big?
おっぱい大きくない?
is that so.
そうですか
Your breasts are big.
おっぱい大きいよね
I'll take a closer look though.
近くでちょっと見ちゃいますけど
Then try it yourself.
じゃあ、自分でもんでみて
It's big, isn't it?
大きいよね
I agree.
そうですね
A little boobs, okay?
ちょっとおっぱいさ、いい?
Try it.
もんでみて
amazing
すごい
hey.
ね
I think you will be touched a lot.
い っぱい触られると思う
It feels good.
気 持ちいい
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
Yeah.
うん
That's naughty.
やらしいね
So beautiful.
すっごい綺麗
Amazing, four sides.
すごい、四つの辺が
Great, wait a minute.
すごい、ちょっと待って
My neck is so dry.
首ビシャビシャになってる
Great, I'm sleeping.
すごい、寝てる
Why are you sleeping so much?
なんでこんなに寝てる?
amazing.
すごい
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
What do you think?
どうだ?
It's thin, amazing.
薄いね、すごい
It has a beautiful color.
綺麗な色してる
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
It's pink.
ピンク色じゃん
So beautiful.
すごい綺麗
Can I open it?
開いてみていい?
amazing.
すごい
It's small.
ちっちゃいね
copper?
どう?
It's cold.
寒いね
oh yeah.
そうそう
It's cold.
寒いね
Can I lick it?
舐めてもいい?
Yeah.
うん
Soft breasts.
柔らかい、おっぱい